http://www.meaningoflife.tv/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the way we collect and use information from visitors to MeaningofLife.tv.
Personal identification information
We do not collect personal information about visitors to our website unless you choose to provide that information to us via our contact form or email subscription (see below).
Contact form
We provide a contact form on MeaningofLife.tv so that site visitors can communicate with us. Users of this optional service provide a name as well as an email address where they can receive a response when one is needed. We do not use this information for any purpose other than responding to inquiries and we do not share this information with third parties.
Email subscriptions
We allow users to subscribe to our content through the email delivery features of Google’s FeedBurner application. Users of this optional service provide an email address where they want to receive MeaningofLife.tv subscription emails. We do not use these email addresses for any purpose other than MeaningofLife.tv email subscriptions and we do not share them with third parties.
Disqus commenting system
We use the Disqus commenting system to collect and display comments about content on MeaningofLife.tv. Disqus is an independent web application with its own privacy policy. If you log in and comment through Disqus, your comments and information, including personal information such as your email address, are subject to the privacy policy of Disqus. We are not responsible for the privacy of information transmitted through the Disqus commenting system, even though it is accessed via our webpages.
We may occasionally look up an email address of a commenter via the administration panel available to us as Disqus moderators, in order to communicate privately with the commenter. We do not use these email addresses for any other purpose and we do not share them with outside parties.
CafePress shop
We sell branded merchandise in our “shop” on the CafePress website. CafePress is an independent website with its own privacy policy. If you purchase merchandise on CafePress, your information, including personal information such as your email address, is subject to the privacy policy of CafePress. We are not responsible for the privacy of information transmitted on CafePress.
Nonpersonal identification information
When you visit MeaningofLife.tv, we automatically gather and store some bits of nonpersonal information about your visit, so we can track the use of our website and make improvements. This information is stored and used in the aggregate only—no data is stored about your own individual visit that can be linked to you personally. The collected information includes:
the type of computer, operating system and browser used to access MeaningofLife.tv
the IP address from which you access MeaningofLife.tv
the internet address of the website from which you navigate to MeaningofLife.tv
the date and time you access MeaningofLife.tv
the pages, files, documents and links that you visit on MeaningofLife.tv
Cookies
Cookies are bits of computer code stored on your own computer by a website that you visit. Cookies are often used to track a website’s usage patterns, traffic trends and user behavior. Many content adjustments and service improvements are made based on the data derived from cookies. Cookies are also sometimes used to save a user’s information so it doesn’t need to be re-entered each time the user visits.
The cookies we use on MeaningofLife.tv do not collect personally identifiable information. Currently we use cookies to limit the frequency with which a user is presented with pre-roll video ads. You may set your browser to refuse cookies from any website you visit. If you choose to do so, you should still have full use of MeaningofLife.tv, but you may see more frequent pre-roll video ads.
We also use the following Google services on MeaningofLife.tv, all of which employ cookies to collect nonpersonal information:
Google Analytics
We use a third-party vendor, Google Analytics, to store and analyze cookies in order to make MeaningofLife.tv more interesting and useful to you. Information that we collect from these cookies is not used to create profiles of individual users and is used only in aggregate form. You may opt out of Google Analytics by using the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.
Google AdSense
AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google. We use this service to display ads on MeaningofLife.tv, which entails using the DoubleClick cookie to track user behavior concerning ads. The DoubleClick cookie enables Google and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to MeaningofLife.tv and/or other sites on the internet. This cookie does not track personal information about you such as your name or email address. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.
Google AdWords
We sometimes use the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third-party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. Such ads could appear on the Google search results page or on a site in the Google Display Network. We also use the “similar audiences” feature of AdWords, which targets our ads to people whose browsing patterns are similar to those of the MeaningofLife.tv audience.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using MeaningofLife.tv, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website.
We may update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes. Your continued use of MeaningofLife.tv following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contact us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please send us a message on our contact form.
This document was last updated on 18 March 2015.
SophiaAre the big questions good questions?Philosophers Daniel Kaufman and Joshua Rasmussen debate whether an all-encompassing epistemology is attainable.Play entire videoPlay this clip The Wright ShowHow did life get so complex?Robert Wright and Massimo Pigliucci discuss the evolution of intelligence and biological complexity.Play entire videoPlay this clip
The Wright ShowCan our species bridge the polarization divide?Robert Wright and Josh Summers consider.Play entire videoPlay this clip SophiaIs it wrong to not vote?Daniel Kaufman speaks with Kevin Currie-Knight, who chose not to vote in the recent election. Play entire videoPlay this clip
MeaningofLife.tv
SophiaDebating standpoint theoryPhilosophers Daniel Kaufman and Crispin Sartwell examine the idea of “standpoint,” which is often deployed in debates over race and gender.Play entire videoPlay this clip The Wright ShowThe LogosRobert Wright and Josh Summers discuss one approach to reconciling science with belief in a higher purpose.
Play entire videoPlay this clip Mind-Body ProblemsThe necessity and dangers of “expertise”John Horgan and historian of science and technology Lee Vinsel discuss real experts and false authorities.Play entire videoPlay this clip The Wright ShowThe tradition of liberal ProtestantismRobert Wright speaks with Guthrie Graves-Fitzsimmons, author of the new book Just Faith: Reclaiming Progressive Christianity.
Play entire videoPlay this clip SophiaA controversial reviewDaniel Kaufman and Robert Gressis discuss Oliver Traldi’s review of philosopher Kate Manne’s new book Entitled, which sparked an online backlash.Play entire videoPlay this clip The Wright ShowHas social media hijacked our minds?Robert Wright and Josh Summers discuss The Social Dilemma, a new documentary highly critical of social media.
Play entire videoPlay this clip
